Sergey Konstantinovsky

Address: Frank 21 Hadera
Phone: 052-4621643

Email: yejonkov@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sergey-konstantinovsky-87268413a/

GitHub: https://github.com/sergkonsta/Bootcamp

Summary:

Fresh out of a software development boot camp in C, 6 years of experience being a system engineer and a team leader, a B.Sc. in Electrical and Electronics Engineering.

I am loyal, self-teaching, trustworthy and motivated team player. Eager to learn, I am currently taking my first steps in the software programming world and looking to be a part of a family.

Educational Qualifications:

• <u>03/2020 – 07/2020 - C Programming boot-camp</u> Infinity-Labs, Ramat-Gan

• 2010 – 2016 - B.Sc. in Electrical and Electronics Engineering

Ort Braude, Karmiel

2009 – 2010 - Practical Engineer in Electrical Engineering
 IAF technical school, Haifa

Projects and skill sets:

Projects:

- "Watchdog" Scheduler and signal based, executable Process Watchdog, in C. As part of C boot camp
- "Scheduler" Heap Priority Queue based, task Scheduler, in C. As part of C boot camp

Languages: C, C++ (basic), Python (basic), Bash (basic), Assembly (basic)

SW: Gedit, Visual Studio Code, PyCharm, Git

Work History:

2016 – 2020 - System Project Engineer - Network division, Israeli Air Force Headquarters

- Project management of access control systems and sites security and defense
- Defining requirement specifications, system architecture and interface, test planning and execution, correction of design flaws
- Leading large scale projects of high complexity as a system engineer

2014 - 2016 - Project Team Manager - Network Division, IAF Base

Managing 2 teams of 22 technicians in total - Network IT team

Languages:

Hebrew - Native speaker, Russian - Native speaker, English - Professional speaker

Military Service:

2014 - 2020 Military service in Israeli air force. Top secret clearance. Honorable discharge as a Captain